sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
dareka no kitai ni zutto kotae
are you really happy
homerarerunoga suki nano desuka
when you're always meeting to someone's expectations?
naritai jibun wo surikaetemo
even if you change to who you really wanna be
egao wa itsudemo suteki desuka
will you always have a great smile?
hajimaridake yume mite okiru
dreaming of only the beginning, I wake up
sono saki nara itsuka jibun no ude de
and someday, I'll live on my own.
souda daiji na mono wa itsumo katachi no nai mono dake
yes, precious things are never in shape
te ni iretemo nakushitemo kizukanumama
you never know what it is when you get it or lose it
sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
Disqualified?!
Danger!
Moving
Ahead of
Schedule!
The Main Tournament
with Troubles!
You...
You did it!
So that fox kid can fight like this...
That was awesome!
Well done!
That was a great fight!
Yay!
And he still has the energy
to run around...
Man... He's got crazy stamina that guy...
That Naruto...
He keeps getting stronger...
He did it... that kid.
Yeah! He's on the right track!
And he's a little cute...
Something about it...
I'm envious of you...
Watching your battle makes me think
that I have to work really hard too...
That's amazing, you know?
He won. Is it for real?
I thought he was the same as me,
in the not going anywhere class...
Not going anywhere?
Now people are squealing...
Looks like he's part of the group
that's going somewhere.
Maybe I couldn't beat him...
This is really bad.
It kinda depresses me...
To retain himself and draw out
the Chakras of the Nine-Tailed Fox...
Yeah... Most of the Leaf Village people
here are surprised.
That Naruto...
When did he learn to control the strength
of Nine-Tailed Fox to that extent?
Even a bird who gets caught,
once it learns how,
will open the lid of its basket
with its own beak.
He won't give up, for he wants to
fly freely in the sky again.
This time you lost!
Father...
It's okay, there's no damage
to his internal organs.
It seems like his Chakra
is almost used up.
You are not the only one special.
Why do you act against
your fate that much?!
Because I was called a failure...
Those who become Hokage
are born to that fate.
So what?!
Hyuga-sama!
I'm sorry but...
Could you step out for a moment?
B-But...
It won't take long.
Y-Yes.
What do you need from me?
That day...
I came to tell you the truth...
about that day.
That day...?
At that time, I intended to die!
W-What are you talking about?!
That day my father...
He was killed
as your body double!
The truth of that day... is here.
They're probably only excuses made
at the convenience of the head family.
The person you are now...
should be able to understand.
This writing...!
Neji... I only have a little time left.
I want to use that limited time
to convey something to you...
Convey something to me?
The head of the Shinobi from the
Land of Lightning,
who was trying to kidnap Hinata-sama,
was killed by Hiashi-sama...
But the Land of Lightning didn't
acknowledge the abduction of Hinata-sama,
made only the killing
of the head Shinobi a problem,
and made unreasonable demands.
It can't be helped.
With my one life,
the village can be saved...
Wait, Hiashi. Don't be so hasty!
The Hyuga's Kekkei Genkai
is an important strength of this land.
It is the duty of the head family
to protect it forever...
However, for the sake of that duty...
if we involve our land
in a desperate war...!
I understand that!
That's why...
Isn't that why
we have branch families?
Hizashi's corpse...
We'll hand it over as your body double.
Hizashi too...
understands the situation.
However, what they want is
the secret of the power of the Byakugan.
The point in time that
Hizashi becomes a corpse,
that power will be sealed.
I don't believe that the Land of Lightning
will consent to that.
That's their true intent,
but the condition made by Lightning is to
"Hand over Hyuga Hiashi's dead body."
We pretend that we agreed
to their terms,
and hand Hizashi,
who is identical to you, over...
and they can't pursue it
any further than that.
B-But...
Hiashi... The time has come...
Your predecessors have done the same
to protect the power of Hyuga clan.
Even siblings...
have the heart to write each other off.
That is the fate of the head family.
And this... is the destiny of
ones born into Hyuga!
Where has Hiashi-sama,
who is always bullish, go?
The scale of this issue is different
from the ones in the past!
It's not that easy...
H-Hizashi... you...
Please... let me go.
You... You... have Neji.
Why do you choose death...
for the head family?!
That's not so!
I have been resenting
the head family.
To tell the truth
even now I'm bitter.
That's why...
I want to die protecting you as
"my brother," not as the head family.
It's the first time I've had
the freedom to choose.
I've only shown Neji my ugly side.
However, now I've come here
and finally know my own intentions.
So please tell Neji...
I-I wasn't killed to protect
the head family...
but to protect my siblings,
family and the land...
by my own will I chose death!
T-To choose death...
you call that freedom...?
Nii-san...
Once, just this once,
I wanted to defy the fate of Hyuga.
I wanted to choose my own fate.
That's all.
Overcome your own fate, Neji...
Fate is something you work out
with your own hands.
Father...
This is... the truth!
I'm sorry!
Please... raise your head.
Father...
I wonder if a person's destiny is
only floating like a cloud in a fixed current...
Or is a person able to ride
on the current that he chooses.
I don't understand it well yet.
Whichever, the end point
might still be the same...
Just, when the choice is the latter...
people turn toward the goal of
living and work hard toward it.
And those who hold that
are really strong.
I feel like I finally understand,
through this battle...
And... father...
I have only one goal...
I want to become stronger,
so I won't lose to anyone.
That's how I feel now.
Father... I see many birds flying.
And they seem to be enjoying themselves.
It's buzzing.
That's because it was a good battle...
Certainly, there's that too, but...
It's likely that, for the curious heads
of Ninja and the feudal lords,
there is no match they look forward to
more than this next match.
By the way, it seems that
he wasn't seen at the opening ceremony...
He's arrived here already, hasn't he?
There's been no news of Sasuke.
And there's the issue of Orochimaru.
Before everyone starts to make noise,
we should disqualify him...
What's going on?!
Hurry up and start the next match!
How long are you going to
make us wait!
Before night falls!
I wonder what's going on
with the next match?
Is Sasuke-kun here?
Sasuke-kun...
That guy...
What in the world is he doing?!
Is he planning
not to show up?
A wise man never courts danger...
A wise judgment... is it?
What are you saying?
He'll definitely come!
But seriously, what is he doing?
Keep this up and he...
he'll be disqualified.
There's no choice...
Sasuke is... disqualified.
Yes.
Uchiha Sasuke is... disqualified?
It has to be done.
What in the world are
we going to do?
If that guy doesn't show up,
our plan of strategy...
This isn't good...
Could he have...?
Where are you going, Gaara?
I'm going to confirm my existence...
Damn that Gaara...
I wonder if he really killed him...
Sasuke one more time...
What happened?
It's obvious that you're there
standing with the thirst for blood.
Why don't you come out?
It's you...
Hokage-dono...
I want you to consider waiting a little bit
for Uchiha Sasuke's disqualification.
I understand your point, but...
No matter how excellent the Shinobi,
to make light of time is not
a qualification for Chunin.
If there's no clear reason to satisfy
the heads of Shinobi and feudal lords
who are here,
there's no reason to wait for him!
I see...
Well then, there is a sufficient reason.
Including myself...
most of the heads of Shinobi and
feudal lords that are here...
came here because
they want to see the next match.
However...
He's the remaining survivor
of the "Uchiha."
Land of the Wind too, absolutely,
is hoping for a bout with our Gaara.
Hokage-sama...
There's no guarantee that
Sasuke will come but...
All right then...
We shall specially postpone
this match and wait.
Hokage-sama! Really...
Inform so to the Proctor!
Y-Yes.
However...
It's rare for you to insist like that,
Kazekage-dono.
Well...
To show off the Shinobi's qualities
of our village to the feudal lords...
there's no better opponent
than an Uchiha.
It's a chance for us as well.
C'mon, what happened to the match?!
What happened to Uchiha?!
I understand...
Everyone! The candidate for the
next battle has not arrived here!
We'll briefly postpone this battle
and start the following battle ahead of it.
What is he doing... that Sasuke?
Great, so Sasuke-kun didn't get disqualified!
That's good...
Hey! That means my match
is one match closer!
Then, on to the next pair!
Kankuro and Aburame Shino!
Come down!
My match... doesn't matter at all.
More importantly...
I'd rather not expose the Mechanism
of Crow to the enemy before the plan...
Proctor!
I abstain!
What?!
Please advance the matches!
Due to Kankuro's abstention,
Aburame Shino wins by default!
What's that all about?!
Have a proper match!
You are...?
It's my turn, isn't it?
It seems that you're really fired up.
Okay, let's go to the next match.
Hey! The last one, come down!
Hey! Hey! What are you doing,
frivolously building things up?
I mean, why does only
my match have to be modified?
Nara Shikamaru! You!
Damn...
If it's like this I'll abstain too...
C'mon! Shikamaru, fight hard!
Damn that Naruto...
ONE JAMPU ichiban SURAMU DANKU kamasu TAISON
One! first, Tyson jumps and slam-dunks
TWO are mo kore mo dosoku de HAGU KISSU I LOVE YOU
Two! he kisses and hugs everyone randomly and says "I love you"
THREE YOGA wo kiwamemasu KAREE kirai masara san
Three! Masala masters yoga but hates curry
FOUR hetare tougyuushi SANCHESU OREI
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter, olay!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
ONE kokuen bori ni bottou bodi ma haattaya san mo
One! Bodimahattaya devotes his time for digging black ships
TWO PEKIN DAKKU waiyaa AKUSHON chari de isogu CHEN RII
Two! peking Duck, action scene, Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
THREE MY KOTEKA daiji ni migakiageru POPO san
Three! Popo loves to polish his coteka
FOUR ote wo haishaku JAPANIIZU PIIPOO
Four! japanese people, now lend me your hand!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
sekaijuu hora kawatteku minna ganbatte so tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Go! Shikamaru!
It looks a bit strange that Shikamaru
is fighting in the Final Round.
He's good, firing up, burning up!
That's my teammate!
But, doesn't he seem spaced out
looking at the sky?
He totally looks so ambitious.
All right, Shikamaru!
Keep it up and
attack hard!
Next time:
"The Clouds are Nice... The Guy with No Interest."
Ino, your cheering is kinda scary.